http://www.weatherexperts.com/website/privacy

Menu
HomeAboutAlden ProductsAE-1000 Compact Navtex ReceiverAE-1800 Professional Navtex ReceiverAE-2000 Professional Navtex ReceiverWiNRADiO WR-G33EM Marine HF ReceiverNavtex and Marinefax AccessoriesDavis InstrumentsWeather StationsData StorageUpdating OptionsContact
Shopping cart is empty.
Privacy Policy
Morcom International, Inc./Alden Weather Systems Division takes seriously the privacy of those that visit our web site. We have established this Privacy
Policy to communicate what information we collect and how that information is used and safeguarded.
By accessing this website (www.alden.com), you acknowledge the terms and conditions expressed herein. We reserve the right to change this policy at our
sole discretion and without notice.
What information is collected, and why?
When a user visits our website, we collect information about the visit that does not identify the user personally. We track information such as the domain
from which the user is visiting and the user's browser type. We also collect specific information regarding the user's session on our website.
This includes items such as the date and time of the visit and the pages viewed.
Sometimes we ask a user to voluntarily provide personally identifiable information (PII). This information generally includes, but is not limited to, name,
e-mail address, postal address, and telephone number. We request this information when the user requests one of the following:
To register to attend an on-line seminar or demonstration
To receive specific information from us such as a whitepaper or code sample
To sign up for a mailing list
To correspond with us
Or any other such activity that we deem necessary
Morcom International, Inc./Alden Weather Systems Division does not collect any personally identifiable financial or health-related information. We do not
intentionally collect information from children under the age of 13.
How is the information used?
Non-personally identifiable information (non-PII) is collected to allow us to analyze how our website is used and to improve the content and service the
website provides.
Personally identifiable information is collected for analysis to improve the content of the website and the services we provide the user.
Morcom International, Inc./Alden Weather Systems Division owns the collected information and will not sell, trade, or rent the information to others. We
may use the information to continue contact with the user. This may include contact such as follow-up calls, e-mail correspondence, or mail
correspondence to follow-up on the contact or to provide marketing information about promotions, new services, or important website changes.
Morcom International, Inc./Alden Weather Systems Division may share this information with its business partners for the specific purpose of
a promotion or service offering.
Are "Cookies" used on the website?
"Cookies" are small pieces of information that are placed on a web user's hard drive. We may use cookies to provide you with better service. Cookies are
pieces of information that a Web site transfers to your computer's hard disk for record-keeping purposes. Cookies can make the Web more useful
by storing information about your preferences for a particular site. The use of cookies is an industry standard, and many major Web sites use
them to provide useful features for their customers. Cookies in and of themselves do not personally identify users, although they do identify
a user's computer. Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies. If you prefer, you can set your browser to refuse cookies. However, you
may not be able to take full advantage of the functionality of the Morcom International, Inc./Alden Weather Systems Division site if you do
so.
How is personally identifiable information safeguarded?
Morcom International, Inc./Alden Weather Systems Division utilizes industry standard methods and mechanisms such as firewalls, intrusion monitoring, and
passwords to protect electronic information. Multiple physical security methods such as locking devices and 24 hour premise monitoring are
also employed. Finally, access to PII is limited to a small number of personnel and on a need-to-know basis.
Links to other web sites
Morcom International, Inc./Alden Weather Systems Division web site may contain links to other internet web sites. Morcom International, Inc./Alden Weather
Systems Division neither controls nor endorses external sites and is not responsible for the content of such sites. This policy does not cover
the privacy policies and data collection practices of non-Morcom International, Inc./Alden Weather Systems Division web sites.
How to opt out of correspondence
Based on the information a user has provided, Morcom International, Inc./Alden Weather Systems Division may send e-mail correspondence to the user. Each
correspondence will contain an easy means to opt out of further correspondence.
Morcom International, Inc
Alden Weather Systems Division
3656 Centerview Drive, Unit # 1
Chantilly, VA 20151
U.S.A.
Toll Free: (800) 683-4101
Phone: (703) 263-9305
Fax: (703) 263-9308
<!--->
